<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<max>
      <!--기본 선택지-->
      <desc id="0" select="1">
        [
        {You see a thick forest that can't have grown up here.}
{At its center is a tree with ripe fruit.}
{You can hear a calm voice in your head.}
{"Relax, have you come here to receive my blessing?"}
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--선택지-->
      <select id="1">
        <node desc="I need it." target="1" isAnswer="false"/>
        <node desc="I don't need it." target="2" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>
      
      <desc id="1" select="2">
        [
        {"If you've never felt the need for someone's blessing, that's a lie."}
{The voice of the tree grows louder as your mind and body get tired.}
{The voice goes beyond the containment chamber and eventually finds you.}
{"I just want to help you all."}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="2" select="0">
        [
       {"I just want to help you all."}
{You didn't say a word in the end.}
{"... you're a bad person if you say you don't need my blessing. There's nothing here for you."}
{The trees disappeared just as fast as they grew.}
        ]
      </desc>

   <select id="2">
        <node desc="Get more people here." target="3" isAnswer="false"/>
        <node desc="Don't get more people." target="4" isAnswer="true"/>
      </select>
      
 <desc id="3" select="0">
        [
       {"I wish more staff would come to me."}
{"All right, all right. You are a fine child, aren't you? I'll give you a present."}
        ]
      </desc>

 <desc id="4" select="0">
        [
       {A blessing is not something that should be exchanged like a gift, but instead should be a wish for happiness.}
{Don't be fascinated by the simple sounds of trees.}
{"How could you refuse my blessing? You're a bad person, I don't need someone like you."}
{Such slyness with these blessings will nourish your mind and body.}
        ]
      </desc>


      <!--스토리 파트에서 출력될 부분-->
      <angela>
        [
        {The spirit of not fearing death fits the Lobotomy Corporation's motto.}
        {But I'm not sure if I can say that it's a good spirit.}
        ]
      </angela>
    </max>