<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<max>
      <!--기본 선택지-->
      <desc id="0" select="1">
        [
        {(The Queen of Hatred looks at you with curious eyes.)}
{"What happened to 'Mr.Employee' who visited me frequently?"}
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--선택지-->
      <select id="1">
        <node desc="Tell the truth." target="1" isAnswer="false"/>
        <node desc="Lie." target="2" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>
      
      <desc id="1" select="2">
        [
        {You inform her that she has hurt employees.}
{"Don't you lie."}
{"I've never hurt anyone innocent."}
{"..."}
{"Wait, actually, I sometimes have these weird gaps in my memory."}
{"And when I snap back, there's always a mess around me."}
{"Then an unfamiliar employee comes to visit me. Not the one that regularly comes."}
{"Nobody tells me what happened to the old one."}
{"..."}
{"Sometimes, people look at me in fear."}
{"But they were so kind to me..."}
{"By the way, did I tell you that I'm a magical girl?"}
{"Yes, I've saved the world from evil."}
{"And I've been here for a long, long time."}
{"Everyone likes me."}
{"But it seems the world doesn't need me anymore."}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="2" select="0">
        [
       {You tell her the employee is busy.}
{"Please tell 'Mr.Employee' to visit me if he's not so busy."}
{"This place is too quiet and boring."}
{"Looks like everyone is pretty busy, huh?"}
{"People I like disappear one by one."}
{"..."}
{"I don't want you to be my friend."}
{"Because one day, you'll disappear too."}
        ]
      </desc>

<select id="2">
        <node desc="The world needs you." target="3" isAnswer="false"/>
        <node desc="The world doesn't need you." target="4" isAnswer="true"/>
      </select>

<desc id="3" select="0">
        [
       {"Then I will continue on protecting the world!"}
{She's too excited to continue the conversation.}
        ]
      </desc>

<desc id="4" select="0">
        [
       {"I thought that might be the case."}
{"It's hard to live if I'm not a hero."}
{"Are you telling me that I have to admit that I'm no longer a magical girl?"}
{She looks down to her feet and is close to tears.}
        ]
      </desc>


      <!--스토리 파트에서 출력될 부분-->
      <angela>
        [
        {The spirit of not fearing death fits the Lobotomy Corporation's motto.}
        {But I'm not sure if I can say that it's a good spirit.}
        ]
      </angela>
    </max>