<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<max>
      <!--기본 선택지-->
      <desc id="0" select="1">
        [
        {A monk is standing silently with beads.}
{"Why did you step into this place?"}
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--선택지-->
      <select id="1">
        <node desc="Greed." target="1" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>
      
      <desc id="1" select="2">
        [
        {"What the hard working people need is a miracle and a savior. I wanted to make it happen."}
{"I wanted to be a good person."} 
{"I wanted to die a good person."} 
{"I wanted to be something."}
{"After a while, they'd all go back to nothing."}
{"I wanted to do something."}
        ]
      </desc>

<select id="2">
        <node desc="Pride." target="2" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>

      <desc id="2" select="3">
        [
       {"Shabby clothes. A shabby cane."}
{"Lost, worn, and old Buddhist scriptures."}
{"I could've afforded it if I wanted to buy a new one, and I could've fixed it if I wanted to rewrite it."}
{"But I left it untouched. No, I tried to leave it untouched."}
{"I didn't mean it, but it's a fake. All of that was from my pride."}
{"I might have been wrong from the beginning."}
        ]
      </desc>

<select id="3">
        <node desc="Envy." target="3" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>

<desc id="3" select="4">
        [
       {"I've done many good deeds, with many good teachings."}
{"There are too many relationships with me. The relationships that have met with me."}
{"Things that will eventually disappear."}
{"Now all you have to do is die."}
{"Everything felt useless."}
        ]
 </desc>
<select id="4">
        <node desc="Eternity." target="4" isAnswer="false"/>
      </select>
<desc id="4" select="5">
        [
       {"Water will not disappear."}
{"Light will not disappear."}
{"It's always different with us."}
{"But I'm going to disappear."}
{"In the end, there's no sign of a struggle to live like this."}
{"I wanted to learn to escape the pain of eternity."}
{"After all, I longed for eternity and failed."}
        ]
 </desc>
<select id="5">
        <node desc="Absolution." target="5" isAnswer="true"/>
      </select>
<desc id="5" select="0">
        [
       {"'Are you a monk?'"}
{"'Are you a monk?'"}
{"'You are no longer a monk.'"}
{"'A demon shall never reach heaven.'"}
{"I couldn't bear the weight of my sins and was crushed."}
{"You are different."}
{"You can get up."}
{"You are a cruel sinner."}
{"Please don't let anyone sway you."}
        ]
 </desc>
   
      

      <!--스토리 파트에서 출력될 부분-->
      <angela>
        [
        {The spirit of not fearing death fits the Lobotomy Corporation's motto.}
        {But I'm not sure if I can say that it's a good spirit.}
        ]
      </angela>
    </max>